[rain pattering]
[Hocheol] Hey, who are you?
You fucking bastard!
Actually, actually, you know what?
Forget it.
I don't really care who you are.
It doesn't matter.
And I won't try to find out, either.
Just give me back the van.
Turn around and come back.
I'm gonna find you tonight anyway.
[scared breathing]
[Hocheol] Then you're done.
[panicked breathing]
[distant thunder cracks]
[grunting and whimpering]
[♪ tense music]
HAPPY! GANGWON
EPISODE 1
BETTING
[doorbell rings quietly]
[grunts]
[groans]
[door beeps]
[Landlady] Hi there.
Is the captain at home?
Oh, he's away for work right now.
Oh, is that right?
It's just, well, the rent.
It's really overdue.
It's been over three months now, right?
You know, we're not just talking about one
or two months.
We're talking about three months.
Look, if he's going through something,
I understand, but...
[inhales sharply]
[Landlady] He could at least tell me
what's going on.
[exhales]
Instead, he ignores all
my calls and my texts.
You two aren't having any problems
or anything, are you?
I know I shouldn't say this to you.
Tell him for me?
CONNECTING CALL...
DOKYUNG
[phone trilling]
[Operator] Your call has been forwarded
to an automated voice messaging...
[phone beeps]
YOU'RE COMING TODAY, RIGHT?
[Man on TV] You're going
to absolutely love this trip.
THE LANDLADY CAME BY ABOUT THE RENT.
[Man on TV] Home to the Mona Lisa.
This is the best that Europe has to offer.
TRAVEL SAFE. SEE YOU LATER
[Woman on TV] Enjoy an easy, rewarding,
and comfortable experience.
And for those of you...
ARRIVING AT 3:00 O'CLOCK
[machine beeping]
I'm sorry but this card was declined.
Are you sure?
Could you just try it one more time,
please?
STYLE
::cue()
[machine beeping]
It's not going through.
Uh, how much is the total?
[Female Automated Voice] Welcome.
Please press the number of the transaction
you would like to complete.
Please enter the amount you...
[button clicks]
NOTICE: INSUFFICIENT ACCOUNT BALANCE.
AVAILABLE BALANCE: KRW 0.
PLEASE CHECK YOUR AVAILABLE BALANCE
BEFORE PROCEEDING WITH THE TRANSACTION.
[Female Automated Voice]
Please take your card.
[distant traffic passing]
[♪ melancholic music]
YOU'RE COMING TODAY, RIGHT?
TRAVEL SAFE. SEE YOU LATER
[exhales sharply]
[cell phone vibrating]
[Dokyung] See you soon.
I love you.
[exhales]
[Heeju] Love you.
[inhales and exhales deeply]
[jet engines roaring]
INTERNATIONAL ARRIVALS
[indistinct chatter]
A404 THAILAND/SUVARNABHUMI
15:00 ARRIVED
[Female Announcer] Attention, passengers.
Final boarding call
for flight 407 to Tokyo.
[indistinct chatter]
[Cheoljung] Hi. I have a question.
Do you know this woman?
[Cheoljung] She works here.
[quiet gasping]
[machines rattling]
[Female Security Officer A] Yes,
we were able to make note
of this shipment but we still have...
[machine beeping]
X-RAY WARNING: WHEN THE EQUIPMENT
IS IN OPERATION,
DO NOT PLACE ANY PART OF YOUR BODY
INSIDE UNDER ANY CIRCUMSTANCES
NO UNAUTHORIZED ENTRY
[Yujin] Belt two, unload the cargo.
[Female Security Officer C]
Which one is it?
[alarm ringing]
[claps]
[Female Security Officer A gasps]
That's right!
Aren't you off this weekend?
We're all going to Sokcho to check out
this hot new night club.
You should come with us!
I've got things to do at home.
[Female Security Officer B]
Oh, come on. No, you don't.
You can't just be cooped up here all
the time.
[Female Security Officer B]
You gotta go out and have fun, too.
Sorry, guys.
I'll join you on the next one.
[all laughing]
She plays hard to get, doesn't she?
[knocking]
You're not here to fool around.
[Yujin] Not without me, you aren't.
[all giggling]
[Female Security Officer A]
Of course you have to come with us!
Where would we go without you?
So where are we going?
[Female Security Officer B]
We're gonna go clubbing, duh!
Wait, Heeju.
-Can we talk for a minute?
-Oh, okay.
Earlier today...
This guy came by and said he
was your uncle.
[Yujin] He showed me an old school photo
of you and asked if I knew you.
He said that an acquaintance of his saw
you working here in your security uniform.
So what did you tell him?
That no one here looks like that.
If he doesn't know,
there's gotta be a reason, right?
Is he really your uncle?
No, he's not.
I thought so.
He just seems kinda odd.
[Yujin] Who was he?
Did you get mixed up with a loan shark?
Uh, no.
It's nothing like that.
Then who was it?
Tell me and maybe I can help you.
You hardly ever talk about yourself.
I'm sorry.
Can I ask...
If that man ever comes back,
could you tell him I don't work here?
I can do that.
Just be careful outside of work, too.
[Yujin] Word of advice.
[Yujin] If you didn't do anything wrong,
don't run away.
Once you start running from guys like him,
you'll end up running your whole life.
Yes.
I appreciate it, ma'am.
STYLE
::cue()
[traffic bustling]
[engines revving]
[car horns honking]
[Woojin whistling]
[exhales]
What do you guys want?
You just had to come all this way here
to find me? Really?
You're a difficult man to reach.
Look, I always repay Geumseong back,
don't I?
I heard it's been a year.
Let's talk it over in Jeongsan.
Well, let's say you go back
to Jeongsan now.
[Woojin] The boys here will have
to clean you out.
Your organs.
They're healthy, right?
What?
It's a joke, man. A joke.
[Woojin] We wouldn't do that to you.
We'll be partners.
Forever and ever.
What do you want me to do now?
Hold your questions.
First up, we need
to check your collateral.
[exhales sharply]
[phone buzzing]
Where have you been?
[Dokyung] I'm still in Bangkok.
What?
-[Heeju] What are you still doing there?
-I'll tell you later.
Where are you now?
Are you home?
[Heeju] Yeah. I just walked in.
Get out of the house right now, Heeju.
What? Why?
[Dokyung] There's no time.
Just get out right now.
Grab whatever you need, clothes, photos,
and get out of there.
Some people are headed
over there right now.
They can't know that you're there.
Some people? Who?
[Dokyung] There's no time to explain!
Just go!
-[Dokyung] Call me after you've left.
-What are you talking about?
H-hello?
[erratic breathing]
Pictures.
Oh, my passport.
Got it.
[doorbell ringing]
[gasps]
[knocking on door]
[ringing and knocking continues]
[beeping]
[Thug A] What the fuck?
Someone lives here.
[Thug B] Ah, dammit.
[Thug C] Hello? Is anyone here?
[Thug A] Look around.
What is this?
[exhales sharply]
-Go check the balcony.
-Ah, shit.
STYLE
::cue()
Nothing here.
[Thug C] You checked everything?
[Thug C] Ah, shit.
Where the hell are they, dammit?
[Thug A] Did you go in there?
[groans]
[whimpering]
[breathing erratically]
[cell phone vibrates]
[gasps]
-Heeju, where are you right now?
-[Heeju] I'm on the bus.
[exhales sharply]
[Heeju] You need to tell me
what's going on.
What do those people want with you?
[Dokyung] Don't worry about them.
It's nothing.
You don't think it's a big deal that
a group of strange men
just barged in through the door?
[exhales]
Talk to me.
What's going on?
I already told you it's okay.
You don't need to worry about it.
[Heeju] Your credit card has been frozen,
and I learned your rent
is overdue by three months.
The landlady came by asking for you.
[Heeju] Dokyung, are you still gambling?
Did you use a loan shark?
[Dokyung] Yeah, I went to a casino
with my friends last year.
How much?
[Heeju] I have a little bit
of money saved.
[exhales sharply]
It wasn't much.
And I paid it off.
[Heeju] Then why did those people come?
[Dokyung] I just paid them back now.
Well then, can I just go back?
No, stay at a hotel.
I'll be there tomorrow.
I know I was supposed to be back today.
But there were some complications
that came up.
Basically, this chairman I know
who lives in Cambodia.
He's Korean.
[Dokyung] And one of his employees
actually passed away in
an accident over here.
We need to ship his body back
to Korea by tomorrow.
But you know how that stuff
can be complicated.
So he called me to ask
if I could help out.
[Heeju] I see.
Are you sure everything's okay?
Nothing will happen to us, right?
[Dokyung] Everything will be fine.
Just trust me.
But Heeju?
I do have one small favor to ask.
The, uh, casket,
the one I'm shipping tomorrow...
Would you be able to handle
the airport security check?
I'm off tomorrow.
[Dokyung] But you can swap shifts
with someone.
I need you to make sure the casket
gets past the checkpoint, okay?
And if the scanners should see something,
just let it through.
[Heeju] Why? What's in it?
[Dokyung] I'm just saying,
in case something goes wrong.
Okay. What could go wrong?
Nothing.
Trust me, Heeju.
Do what I tell you to do.
[Dokyung] Shoot, the chairman is here.
I need to go.
Please don't forget.
Flight A404.
It's departing from Siem Riep
at 7:00 A.M. tomorrow, 'kay?
Love you.
[phone clicks]
Yeah, love you-
[phone beeps]
[exhales sharply]
[♪ suspenseful music]
STYLE
::cue()
[jet engine roaring]
[footsteps echoing]
[nervous chuckle]
-Hi, you guys.
-[Female Security Officer A] Hi, Heeju!
-Hi.
-Come on. Just ask her.
Weren't you off today?
Uh, Yerim and I changed shifts.
Really? Why? Is she okay?
I don't know.
[machine beeps]
Weird. It's not like her to miss a shift.
[Female Security Officer C] Right?
Have you heard anything?
[machines clacking]
[machine beeping]
[inhales and exhales]
[♪ tense, percussive music]
RADIATION CONTROLLED AREA
[OPERATING FACILITY]
NO UNAUTHORIZED ENTRY
[thumping]
[machine belt groaning]
[coffin creaks]
[machine beeping]
What's going on with belt two?
It's all the metal decorations attached
to the casket.
[Yujin] Heeju.
Let it go through.
Okay.
[belt clanging]
[casket groaning]
[all grunting]
[Thug A] One, two, three.
[scraping]
[all exhaling]
[belt strap pulling]
[buckle clicks]
[engines revving]
[Dokyung fumbling with bag]
Long time no see, Captain.
You haven't been to Gold Land much
these days, have you?
You've been up to somethin' big.
[laughs]
If you need any dough,
just let me know and I can help you out.
What am I saying?
You don't need petty cash
from grunts like us.
Sorry.
[chuckles]
[sniffs sharply]
[gun cocks]
The hell is this?
What's it look like?
It's a gun.
[Dokyung] A real gun.
It's fully loaded.
Wanna check?
What?
Look. Look, that exit on the right.
I need you to get off there.
Captain, why are you...
Hey, fucking hell! Hold the wheel!
Hands on the fucking wheel!
[Dokyung] Listen, we're gonna take
the next exit.
-Just take the fucking exit.
-We can't-we can't do this.
I said take the fucking exit, man!
[tires squealing]
[Moonsu] What the fuck?
Where are they going?
[Moonsu] Who the fuck is driving?
[Thug D] Woogy, sir.
[Moonsu] Shit.
STYLE
::cue()
[engine revving]
BOSS
[Dokyung] Hey. Eyes on the road.
Keep going.
[vibrating continues]
I said just focus on driving,
you fucking dumb ass!
Oh, fuck.
[tires squeak]
[Dokyung] Get the fuck out, you asshole.
-Whoa, whoa, whoa, wait, wait.
-What?
Can I at least have my phone? Please?
-Yeah. Call them.
-[grunts]
[car engine revving]
Shit.
Fuckin' asshole!
Fuck you, man!
[door creaks open and shut]
What's going on?
You even called in the boys.
We gotta take care of some meat.
A debtor?
[Hocheol exhales sharply]
Just cutting off parts or butchering?
Butcher as usual.
[drink pours]
Strip him clean
and hand it all over.
We aren't really prepared for that.
You could have warned us.
-Hey, Seokgu!
-[Seokgu] Yes, boss.
Call Mr. Jin and tell him to come over.
-Tell him don't forget his tools.
-Right away, boss. Yes.
[cell phone vibrating]
Who's that?
[laughing]
INCOMING CALL
CAPTAIN LEE DOKYUNG
Hey, Captain.
Have you arrived yet?
Where you at?
[Dokyung] Oh, I guess they haven't
let you know.
I'm the one driving
the funeral van now.
And I managed to shake off all your men.
The casket is safe,
so don't worry about that.
Captain.
What exactly are you saying?
I owe Yes Money two hundred million won,
right?
You agree to write it off
if I help move the casket.
[Hocheol] 212 million.
Well, close enough.
I'm sorry to say,
I don't think that's gonna cut it.
[Dokyung] Also, you really don't want me
hanging around in Korea, right?
I want a billion won in cash.
Then I'll return the casket
and quietly disappear.
[Dokyung] I noticed it was pretty heavy.
That's a lot of drugs.
Must be worth at least 10 billion.
I'm risking my life
to transport this thing.
I want ten percent.
Not a bad deal for shipping cost, right?
You made yourself very clear.
This is gonna take some time, though.
I gotta get approval
from the chairman first.
Then we have to prepare the cash.
You can have up until midnight.
I'll be waiting at Geumsong.
[Dokyung] First I'll check the cash.
And then I'll give you
the location of the van.
Okay. Let's do that.
[inhales and exhales]
[screaming]
[labored breathing]
Fuckin' bastard!
[keyboard clacking]
[cell phone vibrating]
[groans]
[Jinman] Kim Jinman,
Jeongsan Police Investigations.
[Hocheol] It's Park Hocheol.
I need you to track a phone for me.
[Jinman] Whose phone?
What for?
That's none of your business.
You got until midnight.
[Jinman] Oh, come on.
You know that's not the kind
of thing I can do so easily.
[Jinman] I mean, I have to get
a warrant and everything.
[Jinman] It'd be illegal without one.
It involves the Chairman.
[exhales sharply]
Name and phone number.
[Hocheol] Lee Dokyung.
[Jinman] Lee Dokyung.
STYLE
::cue()
[cell phone vibrating]
MOBILE PHONE
DOKYUNG
Hello?
[crickets chirping]
[car engine revving]
[crickets chirping loudly]
[erratic breathing]
[headlights clicking]
[door scrapes]
[Dokyung] Heeju. Heeju.
-Dokyung.
-[Dokyung] Heeju.
[Dokyung] Get in.
[both breathing heavily]
Oh, Heeju!
It's okay. It's okay.
[Dokyung] You must have been scared.
[Heeju] Mm-hmm.
[Dokyung] It's all right.
-You left your phone, right?
-Mm-hmm.
[Dokyung] From now on
we only use these, okay?
[Dokyung] I need you to listen
to me very carefully, Heeju.
I'm gonna go meet up
with someone right now.
[Dokyung] They're gonna give me
some money.
[Dokyung] It's a lot.
Enough for us to leave
this place for good.
A billion won.
-Huh?
-[Dokyung] I'll be right back, okay?
You stay here and wait in the van.
[Dokyung] Then when I call you
on this phone,
all you have to do is bring the van
to the place I tell you.
Wait, what-what are you talking...
[Dokyung] It's not far.
Just listen to me!
If I don't...
If you haven't received a call
from me by midnight,
then take this van and run away.
[Dokyung] And ditch the phone.
As long as you have that casket,
they won't be able to hurt me.
Who are you meeting with?
And what the hell is in that thing?
-Seriously, just tell me what's going on!
-It'll all be over soon.
-You don't need to know about this, Heeju.
-[Heeju] Why?
What aren't you telling me?
[Heeju] Dokyung.
[Heeju] Listen, I will do exactly
as you say.
That's exactly why I need to know.
[Heeju] What am I doing and why?
[Heeju exhales]
[Dokyung sighs]
I'll explain everything later.
When it's over,
the two of us should go to France.
A fresh start.
We'll forget all this.
We can finally be happy. Okay?
I'm begging you.
Please.
[exhales]
[exhales sharply]
Thank you.
[Dokyung] I'll be back.
Just be careful.
[car door opens]
[car door closes]
[♪ dramatic music]
[exhales]
[crickets chirping]
STYLE
::cue()
[car engine revving]
[grunts]
[tires squealing]
[gasps]
Shit.
[Gitae] He must be dead, right?
I hit him pretty damn hard.
[Hocheol] Hey! Go over
and search every inch of the place!
It's there somewhere.
-[Gitae] Get going! Run!
-Ah, fuck.
[whimpering]
[Thug E] Hurry up.
[tires squealing]
[exhales sharply]
[doors creaking]
[keys jingling]
[creaking]
[gasping and crying]
[cell phone vibrating]
[Dokyung breathing heavily]
-[Dokyung] Run away, Heeju.
-Dokyung.
[Dokyung] I'm sorry.
What? No, no, no.
Dokyung, are you there?
Please don't go!
Don't...
[crying]
[exhales]
[door rattling]
[scraping]
[yanking on door handle]
[phone trilling]
Sir, I found the van.
Yeah, it's in the warehouse
at the top on the right.
[whimpers]
Okay, you stay put.
Hey, boss!
[Gitae] They found the van!
[Gitae] We need the keys!
Check and see if the keys are with him.
STYLE
::cue()
No keys here!
Someone's in the van!
Oh, fuck!
[Gitae] Hey, block the van!
Hurry! Move it! Move it!
[tools rattling]
[gasping]
[grunts]
[glass crackling]
[whimpers]
[grunts]
[car engine turns over]
-[grunts]
-[Heeju gasping]
[car engine revving]
[tires squealing]
[groaning]
[screams]
[all shouting]
[tires squealing]
[shouting]
[all shouting]
[crashing]
[shouts]
[breathing heavily]
[groaning]
[Heeju whimpering]
[grunting]
[whimpering]
[engine revving]
[car horn honking]
[all shouting]
[whimpers]
[car horn honking]
[shouts]
[wails]
[tires squealing]
[metal crashing]
[shouting]
[clanging]
[Heeju groans]
[both groaning]
[grunting]
-[Hocheol] Fuck.
-[Gitae] Boss! What the...
[both groaning]
[groaning]
[whimpering]
[breathing heavily]
[gasping]
[tires squealing]
[grunts]
[engine revving]
[Hocheol] Fuck!
[groans]
[gasps]
[grunting]
[roof creaks]
[groans]
[creaking]
[Hocheol grunting]
[panicked breathing]
[glass cracks]
[screams]
[grunts]
[tires squeal]
[Heeju screams]
[grunts]
[gasping]
[shouting]
[screams]
[groaning]
[grunts]
Shit.
[groaning]
[Hocheol breathing heavily]
STYLE
::cue()
[rain pattering]
[breathing heavily]
[cell phone vibrating]
[gasping]
[vibrating continues]
[Hocheol] Hey, who are you?
You fucking bastard.
Ah, actually, actually, you know what?
Forget it.
I don't really care who you are.
It doesn't matter.
And I won't try to find out, either.
Just give me back the van.
Turn around and come back.
[Hocheol] You can have
the money I promised Dokyung.
I can send it right away.
[Dokyung] If you haven't received
a call from me by midnight,
then I need you to take this van
and run away.
And ditch this phone.
As long as you have that casket,
they won't be able to hurt me.
[casket rattling]
[Hocheol] You can't hide from me,
you stupid fuck,
so just hand it over!
I'm gonna find you tonight anyway.
Then you're done.
[gasping]
[phone beeps]
[exhales]
[cell phone trills]
[Female Operator] Your call
has been forwarded
-to an automated voice messaging system.
-[exhales]
[Female Operator] The number you
have dialed is not available.
Son of a bitch.
[whimpering]
[rain pattering on car roof]
[tires squeak]
[car passing]
[exhales]
[car passes]
[thunder cracks]
STYLE
::cue()
[thunder crashes loudly]
[Heeju] Why did it have to be here?
DAD! BE SAFE AGAIN TODAY
[Heeju] I thought I'd never see
this place again.
At first, I didn't expect my path
would be like this.
I only wanted to escape from my miserable
and unhappy life.
Get away from it all.
[thunder cracks]
[Heeju] I was just following this
small ray of light I saw before me.
Hoping that if only I could reach it...
...I could escape from all this darkness.
[thunder cracks]
[9-Year-Old Heeju] Mongsil, wait!
[dog yapping]
Mongsil?
[distant barking]
Mongsil!
Mongsil, here!
[9-Year-Old Heeju] Mongsil!
[Woogy] Heeju.
[9-Year-Old Heeju] Mongsil.
Where are you?
[distant dog yapping]
PROCEED SLOWLY
Mongsil?
Are you there?
[9-Year-Old Heeju grunts]
[9-Year-Old Heeju gasps]
[distant dog barks]
[breathing heavily]
[grunts]
[rocks clattering]
[gasps]
Mongsil.
Mommy.
[crying]
[Heeju] Heeju.
Heeju.
Hurry up now.
You have to run away from here.
[erratic breathing]
[Heeju] I'm still not sure
what I saw back then.
Was it all a dream?
Or was it a memory I made up
for myself when I grew up?
[labored breathing]
[grunting]
STYLE
::cue()
RESTRICTED AREA
[water dripping]
[car approaching]
PROCEED SLOWLY
COMPLY AND DRIVE SLOWLY
INCLINED SHAFT 8, SECTION 2
102ML
[brakes creak]
[car engine shuts off]
[breathing deeply]
[groans]
[Heeju] How did it all end up like this?
Happy. That's all I ever wanted.
To be happy like everyone else.
[exhales sharply]
[keys jingling]
[grunts]
[labored breathing]
As long as you have that casket,
they won't be able to hurt me.
[Dokyung] I need you to take this van
and run away.
[car door opens]
[lid clatters]
[deep breathing]
[exhales and inhales deeply]
[fabric pulls]
[gasps]
[bars clinking]
[clangs]
[Heeju] If I hadn't come here that day...
If I hadn't seen those gold bars
inside that casket,
would I have been happy?
Or would my life be the same,
dark as always,
just like that mine shaft?
[♪ suspenseful music]